Joe,I don't think a four-letter word for "ship" can be "ship."
四個字的船上工作 應該不是「船上工作」
I thought it was a freebie.
我以為那是故意提示
Hello!
What's this?
這是什麼？
Oh,right! It's that girl's phone number.
啊，對了，是那個女生的電話
There it is. Just a phone number...
在這裡，一個粉辣的女生
...a really hot girl gave me.
給我的電話
It's no big deal. I mean, it is her home phone number,but....
也沒什麼，只是她家的電話…
哎唷
Almost lost this baby!
真是的，差點就掉了
The lovely Amanda gives me her number,and I go and drop it.
可愛的亞曼達把電話給我 我卻掉了
Thank you.
謝謝
The One with Joey's New Girlfriend
本集播出：「朋友妻不可戲」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-When's your birthday? -May 5th. Why?
瑞秋，你的生日是幾號？ 5月5號，怎麼？
I'm making a list of birthdays.
我只是在記大家的生日
-Mine's December -Yeah,whatever.
我是12月… 隨便
She's pretty!
她真漂亮
Pretty,pretty girl. The pretty She's pretty.
好漂亮，真…好…真漂亮
Go ask her out.
去約她嘛
-What's the worst that could happen? -I could die.
有什麼大不了的？ 我搞不好會死
Yeah,it's tough being single.
一個人的確很難熬
That's why I'm so glad I found Amanda.
所以我很高興我認識了亞曼達
Ross,you guys went out once.
羅斯，你們只出去過一次
You took your kids to Chuck E. Cheese, and you didn't even kiss her.
你們帶小孩去遊樂城 你連親都沒親她
I tell people secrets.
我會洩露秘密
It makes them like me.
好讓別人喜歡我
All I'm gonna say is,finally,it's nice to be in a mature relationship.
我只是想說 總算來了一段成熟的戀情
You know,the world would be such a better place...
如果你真的只想說這句話
...if that actually was all you were gonna say.
世界會更美好
Phoebe.
菲比
You're sick. You shouldn't play. Go home.
你生病了，別唱了 回家上床休息吧
But I'm unemployed.
但是我失業了
My music is all I really have now.
我只剩下音樂
Well,music and making my own shoes. Pretty,huh?
音樂和自己做鞋子，漂亮吧？
All right,I'm gonna do it.
好，我去
I'm gonna go get shot down.
我去接受槍斃
Any advice?
有什麼建議？
Just be yourself...
展現你的本色
...but not too much.
但是不要太過火
Wish me luck.
祝我好運
Good luck!
加油
Wish it!
請用祝禱的
I was just sitting over there and....
你好，我坐在那裡…
My name's Chandler. Did I say that?
我是錢德，我有說嗎？
No,you didn't. Hi,I'm Kathy.
沒有，你好，我是凱西
-Kathy with a K or a C? -With a K.
凱西是K還是C開頭？ K。
Wow,you are really good at this!
你還真會搭訕
I'm out on a limb here!
別這麼說，我很尷尬
I'm sorry. You're right.
你說得對，我道歉
But I should tell you, I'm waiting for a date.
但是我跟別人有約
And there he is now!
他來了
I see you guys already met.
你們已經認識了
I was trying to demonstrate...
是啊，我正在示範
...how I could get my very large feet...
如何把我那很大的腳
...into my even bigger mouth.
塞進我那更大的嘴裡
Didn't I tell you?
我就說吧
Always showing off.
他最愛現了
Before I start, I want to say that I have a cold.
首先我要說，我感冒了
So if I sneeze during a song, it's not on purpose.
要是我唱到一半打噴嚏 那不是故意的
Except the last verse of "Pepper People."
除了「胡椒人」的最後一句
Smelly cat,smelly cat
臭臭貓，臭臭貓
What are they feeding you?
他們餵你吃什麼？
This chick sounds good.
這聲音不賴喔
Smelly cat
臭臭貓，臭臭…
Gunther,be a good little boy and bring me a whiskey.
阿甘，乖，拿杯威士忌來
At 2:30 a.m.,I didn't expect to have to fight over the remote.
想不到半夜2點半 還要搶遙控器
Sorry,there's this Ernie Kovacs thing I wanted to watch.
對不起 我想看厄尼柯瓦克斯的重播
That's why I got up too.
我也是要看那個
You're kidding? I love him!
不會吧？我愛死他了
My dad made me stay up and watch reruns with him.
我爸以前都逼我熬夜陪他看
Mine too. Did your dad also make you watch the Mr. Universe contest?
我爸也是 你爸也逼你看世界小姐選拔嗎
-No. -Well,me neither.
沒有 我爸也沒有
I'm sorry about this afternoon. If I had known that you two, I never would have....
下午很抱歉 要是知道你們…我也不會…
Oh,please.
道什麼歉
Joey tells me you two met in acting class.
喬伊說你們是在表演課認識的
They teamed us up as partners. Joey picked three scenes for us to do.
對，我們兩個一組 喬伊選了三場戲
All of them had us making out.
三場都是親熱戲
That's a good thing because he used to make me rehearse with him.
太好了，他原先都逼我跟他練
-ls it on? -No,but this Wonder Broom is amazing!
開始了嗎？ 還沒，但是這個伸縮掃把很棒
Oh,my God!
就是它！
It's on!
開始了
Here we go,little fella.
小不點，過來
What about the duck?
那鴨子呢？
The duck can swim.
鴨子會游泳 也對
My sticky shoes
爛泥巴鞋
My sticky,sticky shoes
沾滿爛泥巴的鞋
Why you stick on me?
你為什麼黏著我不放？
Baby
寶貝
Thanks for the lights,honey.
謝謝你的燈光
Way to go!
太精彩了
Your cold makes you sound great.
你的聲音好有磁性
It's fun. God,I love how sexy I am!
好好玩，我真是太性感了
Kath,we should get going. We're going to buy hamsters.
凱西，該走了 我們要去買倉鼠
I love them.
我喜歡倉鼠 倉鼠好可愛
No,it's not like that. I work for a medical researcher.
不是那樣的 我在替一個醫療研究員工作
-Well,have fun. -Okay.
去玩吧 好
It's nice that the medical community...
醫學界總算也在...
...is trying to help sick hamsters.
...救助生病的倉鼠了
-lsn't it? -Yeah,it's great.
是啊 太好了
You know what? I like Kathy.
你知道麼？我喜歡凱西
Me too! She's so cool and pretty.
我也是，她好酷好漂亮
She is.
是啊，她…
She's smart and funny.
她既聰明又風趣
We were up all last night talking. She said the funniest thing about
我們昨晚聊了一整夜 她聊到一些…
What?
怎樣？
You love her.
你愛她
No,I don't.
我沒有
Yes,you do. Chandler loves Kathy.
你有，錢德愛凱西
-Come on,just lay off him. -Thank you.
菲比，饒了他吧 謝了
He's a little sensitive right now because he's so in love!
他現在有點敏感 因為他戀愛了
All right.
Kathy,I love you!
凱西，我愛你
I need to write some depressing stuff to go with my new bluesy voice.
我得寫一些悲情的歌 來配合我的新哭腔
But nothing that sad has ever really happened to me.
但是我沒有悲慘的遭遇
How about your mom dying?
你媽自殺的事呢？
Or having to live on the streets when you were 14?
或是你14歲時流落街頭？
I could write about the time my hair did that whoo-hoo thing.
我可以寫頭髮翹起來那次
I'm going over to Amanda's tonight.
我晚上要去亞曼達家
Rachel's not here.
瑞秋不在
How's it going with her?
你跟她進展如何？
Great,actually. I'm thinking tonight may be the night.
很棒，搞不好今晚就有機會
The kids are gonna play together, and then when they're asleep...
兩個孩子會一起玩 等他們睡了
...I'm thinking Amanda and I break open a bottle of wine...
亞曼達和我再開一瓶酒
...do a little playing ourselves.
我們自己來玩
Hi,guys! This is Josh.
嗨，這是賈許
Josh,these are my friends.
賈許，她們是我的朋友
And that's Ross.
那是羅斯
Dudes.
賈許 你好
You played in college?
你打過校隊？
I still do. Next year,I hope to make varsity.
現在還是，明年我想進大學
Didn't you play soccer in high school?
羅斯，你高中不是踢過足球？
No,wait. You just organized their game schedules on your Commodore 64.
不對 你只是用電腦幫他們排賽程表
It's getting late. I gotta get to the game,so I'm gonna...head.
不早了，我還有球賽 先來閃了
I'll miss you.
我會想你的
Dope!
爽！
Wow! Cute one.
很可愛嘛
-Very cute. -I know. Isn't he great?
非常可愛 我知道，他很棒吧？
So nice to finally be in a fun relationship,you know?
總算來了一段有趣的戀情
There's nothing boring about him.
他一點也不無聊
I bet he's never set foot in a museum.
我敢賭他一定沒進過博物館
Maybe he'll get to go soon.
也許他快要有機會了
Like on a class trip or something.
像校外教學什麼的
You know what else is great about him?
你們知道他還有哪裡好？
What is the word for an adult...
該怎麼形容
...who doesn't have dinosaur toys in their bedroom?
房間裡沒有恐龍玩具的男人？
What was that?
什麼意思？
Monica knows.
摩妮卡知道
It's this dumb thing that Ross made up to try to fool our parents.
那是羅斯發明來唬爸媽的
It's a way of giving the finger without actually having to give it.
其實就是比中指的意思
I cried the night you made that up.
你發明這個手勢讓我哭了
It was the first time I realized I was cooler than my big brother.
我第一次明白我比我哥酷
I'm going to go get ready...
我要去準備…
...for my date tonight...
赴今晚的約了
...so I'll just "head."
先來閃了
I should go too. I'm playing in one hour.
我也該走了，1小時後要上台
You guys should come hear me.
你們應該來聽
Hear me.
來聽
My sticky shoes
爛泥巴鞋…
I lost my sexy phlegm!
我的性感破鑼嗓沒了
Hi,Ben.
班
-You look great! -Thanks.
你好性感 謝謝
Hey,Tommy!
湯米
I am so glad that you could come over tonight.
我好高興你今晚能來
Oh,no. It's my pleasure.
不，這是我的榮幸
My cell phone number is here on the counter.
我的手機號碼在餐檯上
Please,help yourself to anything in the fridge.
冰箱裡的東西自己拿
I appreciate this so much. I have been trying to go out with...
真的很謝謝你
...this guy for a month.
我想約這個男的想了好久
I'd really appreciate it if you'd wait and drink your wine...
我能不能請你...
...after the kids are asleep.
...等孩子睡了再喝酒
I blocked the adult channels for the other babysitters,but the code is four,three
成人頻道鎖碼了 密碼是4…
I'm fine.
不用了
Thanks for this. I hope I can do the same for you sometime.
謝謝你，希望改天我也能幫你
Who wants to make some long-distance calls?
誰想打長途電話？
Kathy! Kathy! Hi!
凱西，凱西，喂
Kathy! Kathy!
凱西，凱西
Kathy!
凱西
Fetch! Fetch it!
讓開，讓開
Kathy! Kathy!
凱西，凱西，凱西
Kathy!
凱西
Chandler,what are you doing here?
錢德，你怎麼在這裡？
I just wanted to say,"Hey!"
我只是來打個招呼
Hey.
好
Okay.
You're making it sound worse than it was.
你說得太嚴重了吧
Her date tipped me $10!
她的男伴給了我10塊錢
What are you doing?
菲比，你幹什麼？
I want to be sexy again, so I'm trying to catch a cold.
我想恢復性感，所以我想感冒
Should be easy. They're pretty common.
應該很容易，感冒很常見
You'll catch pneumonia!
你會得肺炎
Okay,you were right. I'm in love with Joey's girlfriend.
你們說得對 我愛上了喬伊的女朋友
-What? -Are you serious?
什麼？ 真的嗎？
How is that possible? You barely know her.
怎麼可能？你們根本不熟
I don't know. I just
我不曉得，我就是…
I can't get her out of my head.
我就是無法忘掉她
I'm a very bad person. I'm a very,very bad person.
我很糟糕，非常非常糟…
I'm a horrible person.
我是個爛人
"No,you're not. We still love you,Chandler!"
「才不是呢，我們還是愛你」
Phoebe,I think I caught your cold.
菲比，我染上你的感冒了
You mean you stole it!
是偷走才對
Don't cover your mouth when you do that!
打噴嚏不要捂嘴巴
We were just talking about you.
我們正在說你
Really?
真的？
The time you got drunk and fell asleep...
對，就是你喝醉
...with your head in the toilet.
頭泡在馬桶裡睡著那次
Right in there!
泡得剛剛好
-What movie did you get? -I got what I always get.
你們借什麼？ 還是一樣
Die Hard.
「終極警探」
That's what I like about Joey. Any other guy would have been:
我就是喜歡喬伊這一點 其他人都會說...
"Yeah,The English Patient is my favorite movie too."
「我也最喜歡『英倫情人』」
But Joey goes,"No way. Let's get Die Hard.
但喬伊就會說 「才不要，借『終極警探』」
I'm not watching that English crap."
「我才不看那個英國病人」
Yeah,he's dreamy.
是啊，他最棒了
I gotta go. I gotta go meet some friends.
我先走了，我跟朋友有約
He has other friends?
他有別的朋友？
Ninety-nine...
99…
...a hundred. Ready or not,here I come!
...100 我來捉你們了
Let's go over the concept one more time.
我再解釋一次規則
You want to get some dinner with me and Kathy tonight?
小傢伙們 晚上要不要跟我們吃飯？
You know what? I already ate.
我已經吃飽了
It's 4:30.
才4點半
I had a big meal on Monday.
我星期一吃得很飽
So that'll get me straight through the week.
可以撐一整個禮拜
I see what's going on here.
好，我知道是怎麼回事
-You do? -Yeah.
你知道？ 對
You don't like Kathy.
你不喜歡凱西
You got me.
被你猜對了
You've been avoiding her ever since we started going out.
我們交往至今，你一直在躲她
I made an effort to like Janice.
我曾經努力去喜歡珍妮絲
Now I think it's your turn to make an effort to like Kathy by going out with us. Right?
現在該你試著去喜歡凱西 陪我們去吃飯了，對吧？
-Yeah,right. -Good. And hey,my treat.
對，沒錯 很好，而且我請客
-Only because you're not eating,right? -Right.
不過你不吃，對吧？ 對
Sorry,Grandma.
奶奶，對不起
Ross isn't here.
羅斯不在
Stop it!
放手
I'll see you at the party?
那我們派對上見
Beer's fear,man! Twenty-four,seven!
啤酒免費喝到飽！
I am so gonna marry that guy.
我一定會嫁給他
What?
怎麼了？
-I think he's stealing from me. -Why?
我覺得他偷我的錢 為什麼？
Because he's stealing from me!
因為他真的偷我的錢
Hi,it's me...
是我
...and soup.
還有熱湯
I just saw Josh. He looked so yummy in your leather jacket.
賈許穿你的皮衣看起來好帥
I don't eat chicken, so it's just noodle soup.
來，我不吃雞，所以只有湯
There's no chicken in the broth, so it's really just noodle water.
熬湯時又沒放雞，跟水沒兩樣
-Thank you so much. -Sure.
謝謝你
What are you doing?
你拿那個幹嘛？
I need your germs. I want my cold back.
我要你的細菌，我想再感冒
I miss my sexy voice.
我懷念我的性感嗓音
Sorry,Phoebe.
對不起
It's okay.
沒關係
How's the soup?
湯好喝嗎？
Check it out! You can see that girl's underwear.
那個女生的內衣都露出來了
Is she great,or what?
她很棒吧？
What do you think?
你覺得她如何？
She's not really my type.
她不是我的型
Not your type? She's gorgeous.
不是你的型？大美女耶
You know what it is? The fishnet stockings.
因為她穿網襪
Whenever I see a girl in fishnet stockings,it reminds me of...
看到女生穿網襪，我就想到…
...my father in fishnet stockings.
我爸穿網襪的樣子
Understanding a little more of why you're single.
好吧 我有點瞭解你為何單身了
I have a friend you'd like. She's really pretty. And then we could double date.
我有個很漂亮的朋友 我們可以一起約會
No,thanks.
不必了
I've got some ugly friends, and they're all available too.
好 我也有幾個丑朋友沒有對象
I'm gonna grab a beer.
我去叫酒
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
-What was that? -What?
你什麼意思？ 什麼？
Kathy's being really nice and you just walked away.
凱西在示好，你卻掉頭就走
What do you want from me?
你要我怎樣？
I want you to like her.
我要你喜歡她
If that's too damn difficult for you, then the least you could do is pretend.
要是太難了 你起碼可以裝一下
-I am pretending. -Then do it better.
我正在裝啊 那就再像一點
What do you say I go over there and tell her how much I like her?
好，不如我去說我很喜歡她
I can tell her how much I've been thinking of her.
我可以說我一直在想她
I haven't stopped thinking about her since we met.
認識之後我就一直想著她
I'm so over the top, want-to-slit-my-own-throat...
我無可救藥 簡直想掐死自己的愛著她
...in love with her that for every minute...
每一天的每一分每一秒
...I can't believe my own damn bad luck that you met her first!
我都在怨恨為何是你先認識她
That's pretty good.
很不錯
But you might want to tone it down a little.
但是別那麼誇張
I still have a fever? Are you sure that thing's working right?
我還在發燒？ 你確定溫度計沒壞？
Well,we could take it the other way.
我們可以量你的肛溫
So Amanda just dropped me off.
是亞曼達載我來的
That's one of the things I love about her.
我就喜歡她這一點
She's old enough to drive.
成年人可以開車
You're not going to Mom and Dad's tonight?
你晚上不去找爸媽了？
No,sorry.
不了，對不起
Where's Amanda?
亞曼達呢？
Could you get me some cough drops?
瑞秋，幫我拿咳嗽藥水
I'm thinking you could bring her...
我在想 你可以帶她...
...and you guys could go up to your old room and not make out.
..去你的舊房間 然後不上床
Cough drop,please?
羅斯，咳嗽藥水
At least she's not going out with me...
至少她跟我出去
...to get into R-rated movies.
不是為了看限制級電影
Why don't you just marry her?
你怎麼不娶她算了？
Wait,you can't! I forgot. She's not a lesbian.
我忘了，你不行 她不是同性戀
-Amanda and I have a -You have nothing!
亞曼達和我… 什麼都不是
You're not even going out! You're her babysitter.
你們根本沒在約會 你是她的保姆
You have a 12-year-old girl's job!
你在做小女生做的事
That is so sad.
真可悲啊
And what are you laughing at, Miss My-keg-sucking-boyfriend...
你笑什麼 你男朋友還不是..
...-is-stealing-from-me?
..愛喝酒又偷錢
So he stole a couple bucks from me. Big deal!
他偷了幾塊錢又怎樣
At least he got me something with it.
他有買東西給我
That's mine!
那是我的
Would you both please start acting like adults?
你們兩個成熟一點好嗎？
And give me my cough drops!
把咳嗽藥水拿給我
-Fine. -Sorry.
好 對不起
Here.
拿去
Thank you.
At least I made $10 in my relationship.
至少我還賺了10塊錢
You know...?
你…
Parading goats are parading
遊行的山羊在遊行
Parading down the street
在大街上遊行
Parading goats are parading
遊行的山羊在遊行
Leaving little treats
留下小腳印
Does it even work without my sexy voice?
用這種聲音唱還能聽嗎？
I like it.
我喜歡
-Gunther,kiss me. -What?
阿甘，親我
Do it,deputy! Do something!
副警長，快想辦法
We aren't exactly sleeping in here, but do you mind?
我們沒有要睡，但是小聲點
Can I sleep on your couch?
我可以睡你的沙發嗎？
And I'm still waiting
我還在等
For my papier-mache man
我的紙黏土人
Thank you,my babies.
謝謝各位
Rachel?
瑞秋 怎樣？
Did you hear what happened between me and Phoebe?
我不知道你有沒有聽說 我和菲比的事
We kissed. I didn't initiate it, but I also didn't stop it.
我們接吻了 不是我主動的 但我也沒阻止
I've been feeling guilty.
我一直覺得很內疚
Okay.
好
So...
所以…
...are we cool?
我們沒事吧？
Okay.
好
I knew you would understand.
我就知道你會諒解